(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-05T01:23:16.586115",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
おはよう こんにちは こんばんは！
Good morning, good afternoon, good evening, wherever you are in the realms! Welcome!
ERB TVの「Now That's a Bop」へようこそ！
You're watching "Now That's a Bop" on ERB TV!
司会を務めるのは私... おーほっほっほ！
I'm your host... Ohohohoho!
薔薇は紅く、我が心の炎は青く燃え上がる
Roses are red, the fire of my heart is blue,
緋色の女王、そしてJusticeのリーダー！
also known as the Scarlet Queen, the harbinger of order, leader of Justice!
エリザベス・ローズ・ブラッドフレイムです！
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
お会いできて嬉しいですわ！
Lovely to see you, to see you... lovely!
会場には熱狂的なロザリアンの皆さんが集まっています！
We have an excited crowd of Rosarians here! Huzzah!
最高の楽曲を届ける準備万端の
And a great crew ready to bring...
素晴らしいクルーたちもね！
some awesome tunes to you all! Huzzah!
今夜は最高にノリの良い曲をたくさん用意しているわよ
We've got a massive line-up of absolute bops and a half!
今夜の特別なテーマは... 「80年代」！
Tonight, we have a special theme. We are celebrating music from the '80s!
お家で楽しんでいる皆さんも、もし番組が気に入ったらハッシュタグで教えてね
Make sure you folks at home, if you're enjoying the show, please let us know using the hashtag...
#ERBday2026 よ！ これよ！これ！
#ERBday2026! ERBday 2026, right up there, right up there!
OK！ それでは最初の1曲目にいきましょう
Okay! Let's get started with our first bop. Here we go!
準備はいい？ 「フライディ・チャイナタウン」！
Are you ready? "Friday Chinatown"!
フライディ・チャイナタウン
Friday Chinatown
It's so fly-day fly-day china town
It's so fly-day, fly-day, Chinatown
真夜中の人混みに
In the midnight crowd
It's so fly-day fly-day china town
It's so fly-day, fly-day, Chinatown
はじける ネオン サイン
A bursting neon sign
肩にぶつかる外人
A foreigner bumps into my shoulder
ウインクを投げる
And gives me a wink
知らん顔のあなた
You, with your indifferent face,
戸惑いのひとコマ
a moment of confusion.
踊りつかれていっても
Even if I get tired of dancing,
朝まで遊ぶわ
I'll play until the morning.
港の見える場所で
In a place where I can see the harbor,
何か飲みたいのよ
I want to have a drink.
It’s So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
It's So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
ジャスミンに接吻を
A kiss for jasmine
It’s So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
It's So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
私も異国人ね
I'm a foreigner too.
お店に並ぶ絹の
The silk dresses lined up in the store,
ドレスを指さす
pointing at them.
渋い顔のあなた
You, with a stern face,
わがままが言いたい
I want to be selfish.
愛想笑いのおばさん
The smiling lady says,
きっと似合うわと
"It will surely suit you."
どこか静かな場所で
Somewhere quiet,
着替えてみたいのよ
I want to try changing into it.
It’s So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
It's So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
衣擦れの月あかり
The moonlight rustling silk
It’s So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
It's So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
私も異国人ね
I'm a foreigner too.
It’s So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
It's So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
ジャスミンに接吻を
A kiss for jasmine
It’s So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
It's So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
私も異国人ね
I'm a foreigner too.
男のコになりたい
[Song: I Want to Be a Boy]
男のコになりたいのよ 私
I want to be a boy.
星のハイウェイ バイク飛ばし海へ
Riding my bike down the highway of stars to the sea,
アイツの後を つけて行くのさ
following right behind him.
そして夢を 聞きたい
And I want to hear his dreams.
今日一日だけでいい
Just for today, for one single day,
リボンを解いて
untying my ribbon,
男のコにさせておいて
letting me be a boy,
朝まで一緒ね
together until morning.
だけど chance いつか chance
But chance, someday chance,
二人 dance する時には
when the two of us dance,
ふいに女に もどるの
I suddenly return to being a woman.
男のコになりたいのよ なぜか
I want to be a boy, for some reason.
世界中を 自由に旅したい
I want to travel freely all around the world.
バラを一輪 飾るスーツで
In a suit adorned with a single rose,
最後の日を キメルノ
deciding my final day.
今日一日だけでいい
Just for today, for one single day,
すべてを叶えて
fulfilling everything.
女の子には見せない
I want to see the true face
素顔が見たいの
that I don't show as a girl.
そして chance いつか chance
And chance, someday chance,
二人 dance する時には
when the two of us dance,
アイツ好みに なりそう
I might become just the type he likes.
Sweet couple Pi! Pi! Woo be popple Pi! Pi!
今日一日だけでいい
Just for today is fine,
リボンをほどいて
untie my ribbon
男のコにさせといて
and let me be a boy,
朝まで一緒ね
so we can be together until morning.
だけどchance いつかchance
But a chance, someday a chance...
二人dance するときには
When the two of us dance,
ふいに女にもどるの
I suddenly turn back into a girl.
Sweet couple Pi! Pi! Woo be popple Pi! Pi!
Uh uh uh...
懐かしい
A nostalgic
痛みだわ
pain
ずっと前に
that I had forgotten
忘れていた
long ago...
でもあなたを
But when I saw you,
みたとき
when I saw you...
時間だけ後戻りしたの
only time turned back.
しあわせと
Please don't ask
聞かないで
if I am happy.
うそつくのは
Lying
上手じゃない
is not something I'm good at.
友達なら
I have friends,
いるけれど
I have friends, but...
あんなには燃え上がれなくて
I cannot burn with passion like that anymore.
失った
I wonder why
夢だけが
only lost dreams
美しく見えるのは何故かしら
look so beautiful.
過ぎ去った
Even the kindness
優しさも今は
of the past is now...
甘い
a sweet
記憶
memory...
Sweet Memories
Don't kiss me baby
We can never be
So don't add more pain
Please don't hurt me again
I have spent so many
nights
longing for your touch
I have once loved you so much
あの頃は
Back then,
若すぎて
we were too young,
悪戯に
and we hurt each other
傷つけあった二人
playfully.
色あせた
Even the faded
悲しみも今は
sadness is now...
遠い
a distant
記憶
memory...
Sweet Memories
La la la...
Uh uh uh...
失った
I wonder why
夢だけが
only lost dreams
美しく
look so beautiful...
見えるのは何故かしら
...why they look so beautiful?
過ぎ去った
Now even your long-past
優しさも 今は
kindness is just...
甘い
a sweet
記憶
memory,
sweet memories
You are watching ERB TV!
そら 今のパフォーマンスはエレガンスの極み まさにマスタークラスだったわね！
Brilliant, Sora! That was a masterclass in elegance.
私の心は未だにメロメロ ドキドキしてるわ！
My heart is still melting, throbbing!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
みんなと一緒に歌えて、本当にSweetな時間でした！
It was such a sweet time singing with everyone!
確かにSweetな時間 Sweetな思い出... そうね そうそう！
I get it, I get it. A sweet time, sweet memories... Yes, I see, I see!
そして愛らしいネリッサ・レイヴンクロフト！ あなたも今夜は最高に輝いてるわよ！
And the lovely Nerissa Ravencroft! You look absolutely smashing tonight!
あらリズ お上手ね 舞台袖から見ていたけど ついつい一緒に口ずさんじゃったわ
Oh Liz, you're such a flatterer! I was watching from the wings, and I couldn't stop humming along.
おっと！ 二人への質問があるの！ もし二人がユニットを組むとしたらどんな名前にする？ 80年代のチャートに載るような派手なやつをお願い！
Oh! I have a question for you guys. If you two formed a unit, what would your name be? Something flashy for the '80s charts!
うーん そうね...
Hmm, let me think...
私たち共通点があるわよね？ 「ブルー」とか！
Well, we have something in common, don't we? Like 'blue'!
そらさんは伝説的な存在で 私は悪魔... それから...
Sora, you're kind of legendary, and I'm a demon... and then...
「BLUE MEGAMISAMA」なんてどうかしら？
How about 'BLUE MEGAMISAMA'?
「BLUE MEGAMISAMA」！
BLUE MEGAMISAMA!
いいね すごく気に入った！「BLUE MEGAMISAMA」 ビューティフル！クールだわ！
Oh, I like that! I like that a lot. Wow, BLUE MEGAMISAMA! Beautiful, so cool!
そらもう一つ質問よ あなたは誰もが認めるアイドルだけど 今夜はまるで映画スターみたい！
Sora, here's another question for you. We all know you're an idol, but tonight you look like a movie star!
もし80年代の映画に出るとしたら何がいいかしら？
If you were to star in an '80s movie, which one would it be?
「E.T.」！
E.T.!
E.T.！
最高ね！ すごくいいわ！
That's a great one! I love it! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
私が自転車を用意するから そらはカゴに乗ってね！
I'll get my bike and you can hop in the basket, okay? Oh my god!
ネリッサにも質問よ！ あなたはパワフルな声の持ち主だけど 80年代のパワフルなバンドでお気に入りは？
Nerissa, a question for you! You've got a powerful voice, yes? What is your favorite powerful band from the '80s?
パワフルって呼ぶかはわからないけど 答えはわかってるでしょ？ 「The Smiths」よ
I don't know if I'd call them powerful, but you already know the answer before I say it... The Smiths!
そうよね あなたをよく知る私には愚問だったわ！
Yes, I know you well enough that I already knew the answer. That was a silly question of me!
でも素敵な答えよ！ ありがとう！
But that's still a great answer! Thank you!
さて 私は次のワイルドな曲の準備に行かなくちゃ！
Now, I better get going to get ready for the next wild track. Yes, wild!
あとは二人に任せるわ！ まったねー！ バイバーイ！
I'll leave you guys to it! See ya, bye-bye!
You are watching ERB TV!
それでは次の曲にいきましょう！
All right then, let's move on to the next song, darlings!
1、2... コブラ！
One, two... Cobra!
Huzzah!
街を包む
Midnight fog wrapping
midnight fog
the city
孤独な
Lonely
silhouette
動き出せば
once it starts to move
それは まぎれもなく
it's unmistakable
ヤツさ
it's him
コブラ
Cobra
leaving me blue
...bra
Only a few memories after you
背中にまといつく
Clinging to my back,
かげりは
is a shadow...
男という名の
of the story...
物語
known as man.
許されるはずもない
There's no way it can be forgiven,
Peace and Love
空をよぎる
Crossing the sky,
抑えた
is a suppressed...
Violence
薄化粧の Baby
Lightly made-up baby,
独り闇を歩く
walking alone in the darkness,
熱さ
with burning passion.
Cobra, leaving me blue...
Cobra, missing you true...
Cobra, only a few memories after you
ハートに刻まれた
Etched into my heart,
あの日は
that day...
ロマンと呼ぶには
to call it a romance...
熱すぎて
it was far too hot.
巡り巡るはずもない
We can never meet again,
Peace and Love
IT'S LOVE
[Title: IT'S LOVE]
周りにいつも男たち
There are always men around you,
取り巻いてて 悩ましい
surrounding you, oh so alluring.
まるで君は Venus
You are just like Venus.
急に男を磨くのさ
Suddenly, I polish my masculinity,
砂漠の中から見つけだした Jewel
for the jewel I found in the desert.
迎えに行くよ どんなときも
I'll come to pick you up, no matter when,
振り回されても ずっと Crazy for you
even if you lead me on, I'm always crazy for you.
形の消えないつながりを
An invisible, unbreakable bond...
信じたい
I want to believe in it...
Eye to eye
ときには確かめ合いたいよ
Sometimes, I want us to reassure each other.
Don't you know, no, no, IT'S LOVE
小麦色した君の肌
Your sun-kissed, golden skin...
やたら誘う アクション
your actions are so incredibly seductive...
高すぎるよ テンション
and my excitement is soaring way too high.
逢えない夜は目の下に
On nights we can't meet, under my eyes,
黒いエニグマが
a dark enigma...
シャドウを塗りにも来る
comes to paint shadows.
違う匂いじゃ 火がつかない
A different scent won't spark a fire.
スタイル スマイル
Your style, your smile,
まとめて夢中
I'm completely captivated by it all.
形の消えないつながりで
With our invisible, unbreakable bond...
感じたい
I want to feel it...
Heart to heart
ときには確かめ合わなくちゃ
Sometimes, we have to reassure each other.
Don't you know, no, no, IT'S LOVE
飾りたてた SHOWが夜に戻るとき
When the decorated show returns to the night,
酔いざめの涙も見せて降り立つ街に
show me your sober tears on the town we step onto.
放さない
I won't let go,
離れない
I won't leave you,
このままいつまでも
just like this, forever.
ときを重ねていこう
Let's stack up our time together,
そしていつか COME TOGETHER
and someday, let's come together.
形の消えないつながりを
An invisible, unbreakable bond...
信じたい
I want to believe in it...
Eye to eye
ときには確かめ合いたいよ
Sometimes, I want us to reassure each other.
No, don't you know, no, no, no
形の見えない繋がりで感じたい
I want to feel a connection that can't be seen
Heart to heart
時には確かめ合わなくちゃ
Sometimes we have to make sure...
Don't you know, no, no, no, It's Love
You are watching ERBTV!
もしも願いが
If my wishes...
叶うなら
could come true...
吐息を白い
I would turn my breath...
バラに変えて
into white roses.
逢えない日には
On days when we cannot meet,
部屋じゅうに飾りましょう
I will decorate the whole room with them,
貴方を想いながら
while thinking of you...
Darling, I want you
逢いたくて
I miss you so much.
ときめく恋に
With this fluttering love,
駆け出しそうなの
I feel like running to you.
迷子のように
Like a lost child
立ちすくむ
standing frozen in place,
わたしをすぐに 届けてほしくて
I wish I could be delivered to you right away.
ダイヤル回して 手を止めた
I dialed your number, then stopped my hand.
I'm just a woman
Fall in love
If my wishes can be true
Will you change my sighs
To roses, whiter roses
Decorate them for you
Thinkin' 'bout you every night
And find out where I am
I am not living in your heart
Darling, I need you
どうしても
There's a wish...
口に出せない
that I absolutely cannot...
願いがあるのよ
put into words.
土曜の夜と日曜の
Because I always want you...
貴方がいつも 欲しいから
on Saturday nights and Sundays.
ダイヤル回して 手を止めた
I dialed your number, then stopped my hand.
I'm just a woman
Fall in love
Darling, you love me
今すぐに
Right now,
貴方の声が
your voice is...
聞きたくなるのよ
all I want to hear.
両手で 頬を 押さえても
Even if I cover my cheeks with both hands,
途方に暮れる 夜が嫌い
I hate these nights where I'm left at a loss.
ダイヤル回して 手を止めた
I dialed your number, then stopped my hand.
I'm just a woman
Fall in love
Don't you remember
When you were here
Without a thinking
Without even thinking,
We were caught in fire
I've got a love song
But where it goes
but where does it go?
Three loving hearts
are pulling apart of one.
Can't stop you.
Can't hold you.
Can't wait no more.
I'm just a woman,
Fall in love.
Fall in...
...love.
青い
Blue...
水平線を
...horizon...
いま駆け抜けてく
...I'm running past it now.
とぎすまされた
Feeling keenly...
時の流れ
...the flow of time.
Ah ときめきへと
Ah, feeling the excitement...
動き出す世界は
...the world starts to move.
忘れかけてた
The coming of a distant dream...
遠い
...I had almost...
夢の
...forgotten...
訪れ
...about.
Ride On Time
さまよう想いなら
...if they are wandering thoughts...
やさしく受け止めて_
...gently accept them...
そっと包んで
...and softly wrap them up.
Ride On Time
心に火を点けて
...light my heart on fire...
あふれる喜びに
...and flood me with joy...
広がれ Ride On Time
...expanding outward. Ride on time.
僕の_
My...
輝く未来
...shining future...
さあ回りハジめて_
...is starting to turn.
虚ろな日々も
All those hollow days...
すべて
...completely...
愛に
...melt...
溶け込む
...into love.
何という朝
What a morning!
いま すぐ君のもと
Right now, I will go...
届けに行こう
...to deliver it to you...
燃える心
...my burning heart...
迷わず
...with zero hesitation.
Ride On Time
時よ走り出せ_
...time, take off running!
愛よ光り出せ
Love, start shining...
目もくらむ程
...so bright it makes me dizzy.
Ride On Time
心に火を点けて
...light my heart on fire...
飛び立つ魂に
...and send it to my soaring soul.
送るよ Ride On Time
Ride on time.
届けに行こう
Deliver it...
燃える心
...my burning heart...
いまこそ
...right now!
Ride On Time
時よ走り出せ
...time, take off running!
愛よ光り出せ
Love, start shining...
目もくらむ程
...so bright it makes me dizzy.
Ride On Time
心に火を点けて
...light my heart on fire...
飛び立つ魂に_
...and send it to my soaring soul.
送るよ Ride On Time
Ride on time.
Ride On Time
さまよう想いなら
...if they are wandering thoughts...
やさしく受け止めて
...gently accept them...
そっと包んで
...and softly wrap them up.
Ride On Time
心に火を点けて
...light my heart on fire.
...あふれる喜びに応がれ
...cruisin' as our merriment begins,
ride on time
baby we can ride on time
ride on time 時よ走り出せ
Ride on time - takin' off into that rising sun
愛よ光り出せ
watch as you're outshining everyone,
目もくらむほど
yeah, you know ya leave me stunned
Oh yeah
ride on time 心に火を点けて
Ride on time - take my heart out for a spin
飛び立つ魂に
fly until we reach our paradise,
送るよ ride on time
baby we can ride on time
You're watching ERB TV!
I don't know how to dance.
Unbelievable! Are we in a 1980s high school disco?
Oh, disco, disco! Yes, disco!
I love it!
この制服似合ってる？
Does our uniform suit me?
Ooh, it's super cute!
You two look kawaii!
You two look so cute!
But the real question is, is the world ready for such charm?
You've captured the very heart of everyone watching... even mine!
Thank you! Yes!
Is this... is this mustache real?
Hey, hey, hey! Hands off, hands off, hands off!
This here is top-tier Egsozardian craftsmanship!
But, I mustache you a question.
Anyway, anyway...
Korone, I heard you're a tough pooch.
Between you and Marine, who would be the leader of the school?
さあ、ころね！かかってこい！
Alright, Korone! Come at me!
Okay, Marine! Come on!
What the frig?! Break it off, break it off, break it off!
It's fine, it's fine.
This is the '80s, ladies, the '80s.
We settle things with a dance-off!
Dance? Dance? Dance-off!
Which leads me to my next question: Who would win in a dance battle?
Anyway, anyway! I'd love to stay and chat, but I've gotta dash.
Korone, Marine, please lead us into the next song. Cheers, ladies! Let's go!
Okay! Okay!
Hi! Now, what's our next song?
I hear it's a high-energy one!
Alright! It looks like everything's ready!
Se-no! Lend me your energy! Huzzah!
光る雲を突き抜け fly away
Through the shining clouds, I fly away
fly away
身体中に広がるパノラマ\
The panorama spreads throughout my body
顔を蹴られた地球が怒って
Kicked in the face, the Earth gets angry
怒って
Angry
火山を爆発させる\
Making a volcano explode
溶けた氷の中に
Within the melting polar icecaps
恐竜がいたら
If there's a dinosaur,
玉乗り仕込みたいね
I want to train it to balance on a ball
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
何が起きても気分はへのへのカッパ
No matter what happens, I feel like a kappa playing ball
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
胸がパチパチするほど騒ぐ元気玉
As long as my heart beats loud, the energy sphere roars
元気玉
Genki-Dama...
Sparking!
空を急降下 jet coaster
Diving through the sky on a roller coaster
coaster
落ちてゆくよ
I'm falling...
パニックの楽園へ
...into a paradise of panic!
景色 逆さになると 愉快さ
The scenery turns upside-down and I cheer up,
愉快さ
cheer up!
山さえお尻に見える
'Cause even the mountains look like butts!
悩む時間はないよ
There's no time for worrying,
どこかに潜む
'cause somewhere hidden,
「びっくり！」に逢いたいから
there's a surprise and I wanna find it!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
頭カラッポの方が
I'd rather have my head be empty...
夢詰め込める
...so I can stuff it with dreams!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
笑顔ウルトラZで
With a smile that's Ultra-Z,
今日もアイ・ヤ・ヤ・ヤ・ヤ
even today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
何が起きても気分は
No matter what happens...
へのへのカッパ
...I feel like it's no big deal!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
胸がパチパチするほど
Just as loudly as my heart pounds...
騒ぐ元気玉... Sparking!
...the Genki-Dama roars... sparking!
You are watching ERB TV!
Absolutely bonkers! Standing ovation!
And a round of applause for that spectacular energy!
We did it! Welcome to the desk, Nene and Iroha!
Yeah!
リズ！
Liz!
リズ、お誕生日おめでとう！
Liz, happy birthday!
Oh, yes! It's my birthday!
Happy birthday! Happy birthday to you!
Oh, thank you, thank you, thank you!
リズ、とってもパワフルだね！
Liz, you are so powerful!
パワフルなダンス、パワフルな歌唱！
Powerful dancing, powerful singing!
そして、パワフルなポーズね！
And a powerful pose!
Oh, yeah! Very powerful poses.
So cute!
Cute?
ねね、そーキュート、リズ、ラブ！
Nene is so cute! I love you, Liz!
Oh, I love you too, Nene!
ずるい、ずるい、ずるい！
No fair, no fair, no fair!
私も！私も！ラブ、ラブ、ラブ！
Me too! Me too! Love, love, love!
I love you too, Iroha!
We are very powerful!
みんなとってもパワフルだったわ！
Everyone was so powerful!
みんなブロンドヘアー（金髪）だね！
Everyone has blonde hair!
Yeah, blonde hair is super, super, very powerful!
超サイヤ人みたいにね！
Like Super Saiyans!
Super Saiyan blonde hair, you know? Very powerful, very powerful!
Yes!
And I felt everyone's power! And Nene, your energy was like a dragon!
Could you show the viewers your most powerful dragon pose?
ドラゴンポーズ！
Dragon pose!
ガオーッ！
Roar!
ドラゴンマウス！
Dragon mouth!
ガッチンガッチン！
Chomp, chomp!
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Powerful pose!
かっこいい！かっこいい！
So cool! So cool!
Wow, that was incredible!
And Iroha, your focus during that dance was amazing!
Could you demonstrate your finest samurai warrior stance?
OK、見てて！拙者はサムライだよ！
Okay, look! I'm a samurai, you know!
ジャキーン！
Clank!
強い！強い侍だわ！
So strong! A strong samurai!
So strong, strong samurai warrior!
Wow, you both performed in a big group tonight. There were seven of us all together on stage!
Tell me, who was the most chala, carefree member at rehearsals?
えっ、ねね先輩を指差してるの？
Are you pointing at Nene-senpai?
リハーサル中もずっとそうだったよね。ねね先輩、おめでとうございます！
She was always like that during rehearsals too. So, congratulations!
ありがとう...
Thank you...
みんなでやろう、みんなで！
Let's do it together, everyone!
あ、みんなでやろう！
Oh, let's do it together!
イェーイ！オッケー、オッケー！
Yeah! Okay, okay!
せーの！
One, two...
コングラチュレーションズ、スタンディングオベーション！
Congratulations, Standing Ovation!
イェーイ！やった！
Yay, nice!
ねね先輩が一番チャラいわ！
Nene-senpai is the most flashy!
イェーイ！チャラチャラ！
Yay! Flashy, flashy!
キュートでチャラい！最高だわ！
Cute and flashy! It's the best!
チャラチャラ！
Flashy, flashy!
本当に素晴らしい時間だったわね！
That was marvelous! What a marvelous time we had! Yes!
グランドフィナーレの準備をしなくちゃ！すぐに戻ってくるわね！
But sadly, oh no, it's come to our last tune in it!
I must prepare for the grand finale. I shall return very soon, gang.
ねね、いろは、少しの間観客のみんなを楽しませておいてね！二人に、お願いしたよ！
Nene, Iroha, please keep the audience entertained for a moment. Look after them, okay?
オッケー侍たち！また後でね！
Okay! All right, warriors! See you soon!
バイバイ！頑張って！
Bye-bye! Good luck!
さあ、今夜のスターのリズは一体最後に何を見せてくれるんでしょうか？
Now, what kind of final performance will tonight's star, Liz, show us...
ね、楽しみですね！じゃあ皆さん、見るのそのまま、それでは...
We are so excited! Everyone, stay tuned and enjoy the show!
行きましょう！ほい！ You are watching ERB TV!
Let's go! Here we go! You are watching ERB TV!
せーの、バザー！
Ready, Huzzah!
I believe the morning sun
Always gonna shine again and
I believe a pot of gold
Waits at every rainbow's end
I believe in roses kissed with dew
Why shouldn't I believe the same in you?
I believe in make believe
Fairy tales and lucky charms and
I believe in promises
Spoken as you cross your heart
I believe in skies forever blue
Why shouldn't I believe the same in you?
You may say I'm a fool
Feelin' the way that I do
You can call me Pollyanna, say I'm crazy as a loon
I believe in silver linings
And that's why I believe in you
I believe there'll come a day
Maybe it will be tomorrow
When the bluebird flies away
All we have to do is follow
I believe a dream can still come true
Why shouldn't I believe the same in you?
You may say I'm a fool
Feelin' the way that I do
I believe in friends and laughter and the wonders love can do
I believe in songs and magic
And that's why I believe in you
You may say I'm a fool
Feelin' this way about you
There's not much I can do
I'm gonna be this way my life through
'Cause I still believe in miracles, I swear I've seen a few
And the time will surely come when you can see my point of view
I believe in second chances
And that's why I believe in you
Hello, sweethearts!
Lovely to see you, to see you...
...lovely!
What did you think of the first show on ERB TV?
Did you enjoy it?
What did you think of the song choices?
I really hope you loved it as much
as I loved performing with such amazing guests.
Huzzah!
Rosarians, to arms!
Are you ready...
...for the surprise?
I have something...
...lovely...
...to present to all of you!
Here we go!
Three...
...two...
...one!
I have birthday merch!
First up is this!
The beautiful key visual art
of this birthday merch is on a tapestry!
I'm relaxing with Bobby and a cute Rosarian
after a dance workout.
Please display this wonderful retro-style tapestry
and take pictures for me to see, please.
We'd absolutely love to see how you decorate the room with it.
As you visited the TV studio,
make sure to pick up your very own ERB TV mug!
Use it to hydrate while watching me on the telly!
"Mum, I'm on ERB TV!
Hey, Mum! I'm on the telly!"
I go saying that, and most likely right now,
Queen Mother is watching this on the telly.
Next, you've all been wanting this,
and so have I...
...a Rosarian plushie!
I'm so freaking happy!
My adventures have been nothing
without my loyal, amazing Rosarians.
Now you can have your very own
Rosarian Bloodflame Kingdom powerful pooch.
I am your sword, and you are my shield.
We are powerful...
...together!
That's right!
Next, we have a set of four pin badges!
You all know...
...I love collecting pin badges,
and here's some new ones for you to collect.
We have the ERB TV logo badge,
shield badge,
Rosarian paw,
and a Rosarian with a headband on saying BFK...
...Bloodflame Kingdom, represent!
You all look amazing with an '80s headband on, I must say.
Lastly,
I recorded another voice pack in both English and Japanese.
The voice pack is called "Exercise with Elizabeth".
So join me on our training arc as we exercise together.
Onwards and upwards!
Then, if you purchase the whole set...
...the full shebang...
...there's a full set purchase bonus!
You get a postcard...
...with the key visual on it,
but that's not all!
The limited quantity includes...
...a postcard with a handwritten signature
by yours truly!
Please do not worry.
Even when those run out,
you still get the postcard with my replica signature.
And that is the full set of my birthday merch!
What do you think?
There's been a lot of love
put into this merch,
and I especially can't wait to cuddle my own Rosarian plushie!
Well, before we wrap up,
I'd like to give a special thanks to the guests.
It is an honor performing with you all.
I'll treasure these sweet memories forever.
Thank you to the crew.
Amazing job, everyone!
Thank you to my dance teachers
who made the choreos.
I hope I made you proud
with my moving and grooving.
Most of all,
thank you, my beautiful kingdom, my Rosarians,
for checking out my first birthday live...
...first ERB TV show.
Those were some bops and a half, right?
Okay, make sure to eat your nums,
hydrate, get good sleeps,
because we want our kingdom to be good and strong!
I love you all very much.
And most of all...
...let my voice...
...be your strength!
Bye-bye!
You are watching ERB TV!
イロドリ
Irodori